<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>The POW Project</title><link>https://ghlearner.github.io</link><description>Questions they asked me</description><copyright>The POW Project</copyright><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://github.githubassets.com/favicons/favicon.svg</url><title>avatar</title><link>https://ghlearner.github.io</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 12:22:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><managingEditor>The POW Project</managingEditor><ttl>60</ttl><webMaster>The POW Project</webMaster><item><title>Do you know how I get rich?</title><link>https://ghlearner.github.io/post/Do%20you%20know%20how%20I%20get%20rich-.html</link><description>Nov-11-2024
NC: Do you know how I become rich?
Me: No. Do share. 
NC: I trade crypto. Have you heard about Shiba coin and Dogecoin? 
Me: No (I lied. I made hundred dollars off it when it’s going up and lost all of them on the way down). 
NC: I made 360000 when I traded them and bought my second house. I just launched my own crypto last night. 
Me: Really? That’s awesome. What’s it called? And which platform did you use?
NC: It’s MAGAA coin. Don’t get me wrong. I am not his fan. But he is popular now. He is the crypto president. People will buy. I will make lots of money. I want to become a millionaire by December next year. 
Hats off to him. This guy is the first and only person I know that is not happy with the election result but taking actions to make things better for himself.。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ghlearner.github.io/post/Do%20you%20know%20how%20I%20get%20rich-.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 12:21:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Do you drive a blue Mercedes?</title><link>https://ghlearner.github.io/post/Do%20you%20drive%20a%20blue%20Mercedes-.html</link><description>Pt: Do you drive a blue Mercedes?&#13;
Me: No. I wish I do. I drive a Toyota Corolla, the cheapest trim. What do you drive?&#13;
Pt: Port authority.&#13;
Pt: Listen, when is your break? I have thirty dollars in my pocket, can you go to GetGo buy me a pack of cigarettes?&#13;
Me: Sorry Sir. I usually don't have time leave the hospital on my break. I have other patients.&#13;
Pt:......&#13;
This is the second time I take care of this patient. CF had a special order for 15 minutes smoke break during last admission. I guess that's the way the doctors try to boost his compliance to treatment. CF has lung cancer that metastasized to the his brain. He got SRS (stereotatic radio surgery) and lost lots of hair, this time he looks like a Mohican. He still drifts in and out of a shelter due to his homelessness. The care team is trying to get contact with his brother and talk about the goal of care. &#13;
&#13;
。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://ghlearner.github.io/post/Do%20you%20drive%20a%20blue%20Mercedes-.html</guid><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 03:47:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>